http://www.highlinerfoods.com/en/legal-notice-privacy-policy.aspx

Legal Notice & Privacy Policy
Your use and access to this site is subject to the following terms and conditions and all applicable laws. By viewing or using this site, you agree to be bound by these terms, conditions, and laws. If you do not agree with any term in this Legal Notice or the Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. All content (everything you see, read, or hear) on this website is owned or controlled by High Liner Foods Incorporated. Worldwide copyright laws protect all content on this site. Unless we provide you with express permission to do otherwise on this website with respect to specific information, you may download content only for your personal use for non-commercial purposes, but no modification, other use, or further reproduction of the content is permitted. Please note that High Liner Foods conducts business primarily in North America. We operate facilities in Nova Scotia, California, Massachusetts, New Hampshire and Virginia. We make no representations that the contents of this site will be available or appropriate in every jurisdiction in which this site may be accessed. You are responsible for any laws governing use of a website. We use reasonable efforts to include up-to-date and accurate information in this website, but we make no representations, warranties, or assurances as to the accuracy, currency, or completeness of the information provided. High Liner Foods Incorporated shall not be liable for any damages or injury resulting from your access to, or inability to access, this site, or from your reliance on any information provided at this site. This website may provide links or references to other sites. High Liner Foods makes no representations, warranties or assurances as to any information in such sites and has no responsibility for their content and shall not be liable for any damages or injury arising from that content. Any links to other sites are provided only as a convenience to the users of our site. We do not endorse the materials presented on sites which are not operated by us. The trademarks, service marks, trade names, trade dress and products represented on this site are protected in Canada, the United States, and internationally. No use of these may be made without prior, written authorization of High Liner Foods, except to identify our products and services. While we welcome your comments and feedback on this site, and we appreciate hearing your recipe and food preparation ideas, we emphasize that we cannot protect your unsolicited ideas, suggestions or materials related to our products, and we reserve the right to share non-personal information received via this site with the public. We do not seek unsolicited ideas, suggestions or materials related to our products. If you do not want us to use your ideas, please do not submit them to us. Senders of communications to this site or otherwise to High Liner Foods Inc. shall be responsible for the content and information contained therein, including its legality, truthfulness, and accuracy. The information collected by High Liner Foods whether submitted to us via a feedback form or through a visitor's use of our site is used by High Liner Foods Inc. solely for internal purposes including, without limitation, marketing, promotional, and feedback purposes. We do not sell or distribute email addresses or other information that may identify you to other parties. Privacy Policy This website is owned and operated by High Liner Foods Incorporated, of Canada. This website is maintained, designed and offered primarily for residents of Canada. Here at High Liner, we recognize that people are concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. Our Privacy Policy is based on Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, and The Canadian Standards Association's Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information. It also reflects our own belief's about what is the right thing to do. We may update this Policy from time to time, so please check back if you are a regular visitor. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: High Liner Foods Incorporated PO Box 910 100 Battery Point Lunenburg, Nova Scotia B0J 2C0 Attention: Privacy Compliance Officer (Legal Department) 1-902-634-8811 highlinerfoods.com Our offices are open from 7:30 a.m. to 3:30 p.m. Eastern Time, Monday through Friday. Please feel free to email us anytime. We'll be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns. Our Policy At our website, we do not collect personally identifiable information from people unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not require you to register or provide information to us in order to view our site. If you register in order to receive the "Investor Alerts" or if you use the "Contact Us" features of this site, we use the information you supply for the purpose of providing the services you have requested. If you specifically agree to follow-up contacts by us or asked to be put on our mailing list when you signed up, we may also contact you from time to time. You can always change your preference for follow-up contacts just by clicking on "change" or "unsubscribe" on the "Investor Alerts" page or by emailing us at any time at info@highlinerfoods.com. We may put together information about our users in a way that your personal identity would not be revealed and then share that information with some of our business partners. We will not share information that might reveal your identity with anyone outside of High Liner Foods Incorporated. In the "Contact Us" section of this site, we ask for some personally identifiable information, such as your name, address and phone number. We use this information only if we need to contact you directly because our attempts to contact you by email were unsuccessful. We do not use the information internally for any other purposes and we do not share it with anyone outside of High Liner Foods Incorporated. We do not use your e-mail address for any purpose other than responding to the message you have sent or email communication you have agreed to receive. Our site sometimes includes notices of contests or other promotions we are conducting and we may permit you to enter electronically in some cases. If that occurs, we will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion (e.g. to contact you if you are a winner). We do not share the information you give us with anyone outside of High Liner Foods Incorporated, except with third party service providers to High Liner, such as contest management firms, who are contractually bound to protect your privacy in the same manner that we do. Personal Information of Minor Children Important Note to Parents: We do not include information or content on this site that is intentionally directed at minor children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from kids on our sites. All of our contests require that participants be adults. Important Note to Children: Before providing your name, address, email address, or any other personal information to anyone on the Internet, be sure to ask your parents if it is okay. Cookies High Liner may use "cookie" technology to obtain non-personal information from visitors to this site. Cookies are information files that your web browser places on your computer when you visit a website. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but can be configured not to accept them or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. We do not extract personal information in this process nor do we provide this information to third parties. Cookies allow us to customize your user interface to speed up the navigation process and to make the site experience more efficient. If your browser is configured to reject cookies, you will not be able to use the features of our sites. When you log in, a cookie can tell us whether you've visited us before or are a new visitor. We do use the cookie to help us identify site features in which you have the greatest interest, so that we can provide you with more of what you want. Links Our site may contain links to other sites. We make every effort to link only to websites that share our high standards. We try our best to ensure these links are reputable, but the privacy and data collection practices on any linked websites are entirely separate from High Liner and are not covered by this Policy. Other websites that may contain material that we do not approve of may also link to this site without High Liner's knowledge or consent. High Liner has no responsibility for the content, policies or actions of these websites.
